http://www.vauxhall.co.uk/tools/privacy-policy.html

£16,440.00
Stunning design. Brand new engines. Exciting tech. Corsa’s back – and it’s now available to test drive. Oh, and did we mention it’s gone electric too?
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Stunning design. Brand new engines. Exciting tech. Corsa’s back – and it’s now available to test drive. Oh, and did we mention it’s gone electric too?
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
All-new Mokka
FROM
£20,735.00
The brand new face of Vauxhall design. Unmistakable style. Full of the latest technology. Comfy and exciting to drive. And a fully electric engine available too. All-new Mokka ticks all the boxes.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
RESERVE TODAY
The brand new face of Vauxhall design. Unmistakable style. Full of the latest technology. Comfy and exciting to drive. And a fully electric engine available too. All-new Mokka ticks all the boxes.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
RESERVE TODAY
New Astra
FROM
£18,890.00
Meet our most efficient Astra yet. And one of the most aerodynamic compact cars on the market. Packed with innovative tech, new Astra is more practical and more comfortable. Enjoy.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Meet our most efficient Astra yet. And one of the most aerodynamic compact cars on the market. Packed with innovative tech, new Astra is more practical and more comfortable. Enjoy.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
New Astra Sports Tourer
FROM
£20,540.00
Sometimes you just need a little extra – whether it’s added flexibility or even more space. The New Astra Sports Tourer gives you all this and a whole lot more. Load it up and off you go.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Sometimes you just need a little extra – whether it’s added flexibility or even more space. The New Astra Sports Tourer gives you all this and a whole lot more. Load it up and off you go.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Combo Life
FROM
£23,010.00
With loads of space, premium comfort, smart safety features and a choice of 5 or 7-seats, Combo Life is ideal for the whole family. For weekends away, trips to the seaside or camping adventures… Make the most out of life.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
With loads of space, premium comfort, smart safety features and a choice of 5 or 7-seats, Combo Life is ideal for the whole family. For weekends away, trips to the seaside or camping adventures… Make the most out of life.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Crossland X
FROM
£19,330.00
A stylish crossover with SUV looks, efficient engines, premium innovations and flexible space.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
A stylish crossover with SUV looks, efficient engines, premium innovations and flexible space.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Grandland X
FROM
£24,600.00
Luxurious. Spacious. Stylish. This bold and powerful SUV is bristling with cutting-edge technologies and ready for action. Anywhere.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Luxurious. Spacious. Stylish. This bold and powerful SUV is bristling with cutting-edge technologies and ready for action. Anywhere.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
New Insignia
FROM
£20,045.00
Bold new exterior. New driver safety tech. Refreshed interior. Superbly engineered. Find out more about the large family car that’s also a luxury cruiser.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Bold new exterior. New driver safety tech. Refreshed interior. Superbly engineered. Find out more about the large family car that’s also a luxury cruiser.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Vivaro Life
FROM
£34,165.00
With its premium appearance, family-friendly interior and attention to detail, Vivaro Life combines everyday practicality with style.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
With its premium appearance, family-friendly interior and attention to detail, Vivaro Life combines everyday practicality with style.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
All-new Corsa
All-new Corsa
FROM
£16,440.00
Overview
£18,483.33
Meet the multi award-winning Combo Panel Van. Keeping your business on the road for less with class-leading fuel economy. Available to order now.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Meet the multi award-winning Combo Panel Van. Keeping your business on the road for less with class-leading fuel economy. Available to order now.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Vivaro
FROM
£24,378.33
More practicality. More choice. More clever features. And with class-leading fuel economy. Discover the ultimate all-rounder.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
More practicality. More choice. More clever features. And with class-leading fuel economy. Discover the ultimate all-rounder.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
MOVANO
FROM
£29,558.33
Sharper looks, more fuel efficient, class-leading payload – the Movano brings it all together.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Sharper looks, more fuel efficient, class-leading payload – the Movano brings it all together.
EXPLORE
BUILD & PRICE
REQUEST A QUOTE
MOVANO CONVERSIONS
FROM
£
Movano Platform Cab, Chassis Cab and Crew Cab. Three solid bases for our three factory conversions – box van, tipper or dropside. All backed up with a 100,000 mile / three year warranty for added peace of mind.
EXPLORE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Movano Platform Cab, Chassis Cab and Crew Cab. Three solid bases for our three factory conversions – box van, tipper or dropside. All backed up with a 100,000 mile / three year warranty for added peace of mind.
EXPLORE
REQUEST A QUOTE
Combo
Combo
FROM
£18,483.33
Overview
Features
New Corsa-e
Grandland X Hybrid (FWD)
Grandland X Hybrid4 (AWD)
New Vivaro-e
New Mokka-e
All-new Corsa
New Mokka
Grandland X
New Astra
New Astra Sports Tourer
New Insignia
Pricing
What is Motability?
Adapt Your Car
Help Me Choose
Motability Help Centre
Owners
Back to Start
Owners
Maintenance & Repair
Owners
Owners' Manuals
Need Help?
Back to Start
Need Help?
Help Centre
Contact Us
Need Help?
Contact Us
Sales Enquiries
Customer Care
Fleet & Company Car
Tools & Services
Back to Start
Tools & Services
Build & Price
BROCHURE
This website uses cookies:
The cookie settings on this website are set to "allow all cookies". This is so that we can give you the very best experience while you're on our website. You can adjust your cookie settings at any time in your browser preferences. Otherwise, we'll assume you're OK to continue. Find out more
Information about cookies
Privacy & Legal
Find a Retailer
CARS
VANS
USED
OFFERS & FINANCE
FLEET
PRINT
This website is owned by Vauxhall Motors Limited (“Vauxhall”, “we” or “us”). The registered office of Vauxhall is at MP UK1-101-135, Luton Road, Chalton, Luton, Bedfordshire, LU4 9TT. This website is hosted in Europe by our IT-service provider Netcentric AG, Prime Tower, Hardstrasse 201 8005 Zurich, Switzerland.
Please read this policy carefully before using this website because it explains how we will process personal information. Using this website indicates that you accept this policy.
1. Types of data being processed / Links to other websites or applications
We care about your privacy. We collect and process various types of personal information via this website, our applications and other sources.  This includes:
Information you provide to us when you interact with us whether as a customer, prospective customer, Vauxhall driver or are taking part in a Vauxhall Retailer programme
Information you provide to us when requesting and using our services and our websites or applications, such as name, address, e-mail address
Information that we need when you report a problem with our websites or applications
Information collected by cookies
Information about your vehicle and specific contract data that we need for the performance of the website (e.g. purchase date, service dates) so that we can provide a positive user experience and the best service for your vehicle
For further details, see section 2.
This website can also contain links to other Vauxhall or Groupe PSA websites/applications or to websites/applications of our Vauxhall Retailers, authorised workshops, other affiliated companies or social media websites. When you click on such a link to any of such other Vauxhall or third party websites/applications, please be aware that these websites/applications have their own data protection policies. Please check their privacy policies when using these websites/applications.
This website can also contain iFrames with content of other Vauxhall or Groupe PSA websites or of websites of third parties. Vauxhall is not responsible for third-party content presented in iFrames. The information presented therein is the sole responsibility of those website owners. Vauxhall has no control or responsibility for the content of independent websites and provides this external content to its visitors for their convenience. As a result, when you visit a page containing such content, you may be presented with cookies from these third party websites. Vauxhall does not control the distribution of these cookies. Please check the Cookies Policy of Vauxhall or the third party's privacy policy for more information.
Please be informed that Vauxhall cannot accept any responsibility or liability for third party websites or applications.
2. Information about the personal information we process and how long we keep it for
Data protection law sets out a number of conditions which organisations can rely on in order to lawfully handle personal information. The conditions we rely on are as follows:
Performance of a contract
Depending on the nature of your request some information may be mandatory. Where possible we will mark these details with an *. This is the case where the handling of your personal information is necessary to enable us to perform our contractual obligations to you. If you don’t provide this information we cannot fulfil your request or perform our part of the contract.
Your contract with Vauxhall may include support or cover for a specified period of time. In these situations Vauxhall or their appointed service provider will endeavour to advise you of the expiry date prior to your cover ending so that you can consider extending your cover if you desire.
Legitimate interests
The law permits Vauxhall to handle your personal information where necessary in our legitimate interests, provided that this isn’t outweighed by your interests. Many of the purposes where we handle your personal information, described below, fall into this category as they are essential activities which enable us to run our business efficiently and effectively. We may, if necessary, also use your personal information to defend legal rights or to obtain legal advice and to manage any complaint that you might have. We ensure that your rights and interests are protected when we do this.
Consent
Vauxhall use your personal information when you consent for us to do so (e.g for direct marketing purposes). If you choose to provide special category data such as information about trade union membership to prove eligibility for Partners Programmes for example, you allow us to use this.
Where we rely on consent as the lawful basis for processing your personal information, you can withdraw your consent at any time. The withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of processing carried out before the date on which it was withdrawn.
Required by law
Vauxhall will, if required by law, disclose your personal information in response to a court order. We will disclose your personal information if requested by a law enforcement agency or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, non-compliance with Vauxhall Terms or otherwise as permitted or required by law and consistent with legal requirements.
Your personal information will be processed to administer and fulfil your request, for general administration purposes and for the purposes described below by Vauxhall as controller.
We as controllers process your personal information as follows:
The information we use (mandatory data is marked with an *)
Why we use it
Your name and contact details
(name*, email address*; phone no, postal address,  model of interest details*, preferred Vauxhall Retailer, leasing / financing interest, enquiry type, fleet specific data
To manage our relationship with you, to contact you including for marketing, customer satisfaction surveys and otherwise, for request fulfilment and for analysis and research to help us to improve our products and services
Your name and contact details
(name*, email address*)
To send you our Newsletter and to manage subscriptions and preferences
Your name and contact details
(name*, email address*; phone no., postal address, contact preferences), vehicle identification data* (e.g. vehicle identification number (VIN), registration number / license plate, first registration date), product and service specifications (e.g. model, trim, engine), service type*, odometer reading, vehicle drop off date/time, pickup date/time, courtesy car
For service request fulfilment
Your name and contact details*, vehicle identification data*, respective product specifications*, odometer reading
For vehicle valuation requests
Your name and contact details
(name*, email address, postal address, phone no.)
To fulfil your request e.g. to arrange your test drive, provide a quote or brochure or to enter you into a prize draw
Information collected via cookies
• Please see our Cookie Policy  for more information.
Information provided as part of programme participation for example Partners Programme- employer name, employee name and your relationship to employee. This includes information you choose to provide to prove your eligibility to take part in the programme
To validate eligibility for the programme and manage and administer our partners programmes.
Information you supply about your vehicle including vehicle identification number (VIN), registration number, diagnostic trouble codes, service dates, expected replacement dates etc
For audit and reporting purposed to help us manage our business effectively.
Your name and contact details
(name*, email address*; phone no., postal address, contact preferences), vehicle identification data* (e.g. vehicle identification number (VIN), registration number / license plate, first registration date), product and service specifications (e.g. model, trim, engine), service type*, odometer reading
To help you set up your MyVauxhall account giving you access to Vauxhall Connected services - and for the ongoing administration of them.
The data elements marked with an asterisk (*) are mandatory and a contractual requirement. You are therefore obliged to provide this information. If you don’t provide it, we cannot fulfil your request.
Based on your user behaviour by browsing on our website, a pop-in might be shown to you offering a test drive or a voucher for your model of interest.
We will keep your personal information whilst we have an ongoing relationship with you and for ten years after our contractual relationship has been terminated. If you have provided your consent for marketing purposes, your personal information will be stored for these purposes for three years after the last contact with us.
A. We will share your personal information for the purposes listed below to the following key recipients:  Where necessary to enable us to perform our contract with you or to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract
The information we share
Why we share it
Who we share it with
Your full name, date of birth and contact details*, vehicle identification data*, respective product and service specifications*, enquiry details, preferred Vauxhall Retailer#, leasing / financing interest, fleet specific data
To contact you, to enable us to fulfil requests and to manage our newsletter and subscriptions
Opel Automobile GmbH, Bahnhofsplatz, 65423 Ruesselsheim am Main, Germany, PSA Automobiles SA, 2-10 Boulevard de l’Europe, 78 300 Poissy, France and your selected Vauxhall Retailer, or the Retailer we feel is best placed to help you. For example if your preferred Retailer ceases trading or leaves the Vauxhall network we will pass your contact details to an alternative Retailer who will be able to contact you to offer assistance.
In some cases sub processors may be engaged who are located outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) in a country which may not have data protection laws as stringent as those in place in the UK. Where there is no adequacy decision of the European Commission, appropriate safeguards will be in place to protect your personal information. In many cases, as below, the protection in place will be Binding Corporate Rules (BCRs). Where this is the case, you can access the BCRs using the link shown in brackets ( ) below.
The above listed recipients disclose your personal information data to the followingIT service providers to support the administration of the purposes described above:
· Capgemini (Capgemini Technology Services, 5/7 rue Frédéric Clavel – 92287 Suresnes Cedex - France) (  https://www.capgemini.com/resources/capgemini-binding-corporate-rules/ )
· Atos (Atos SE, River Ouest, 80 Quai Voltaire, 95877 Bezons cedex, France) ( https://atos.net/content/dam/global/documents/atos-binding-corporate-rules.pdf )
· Salesforce (Salesforce.com EMEA Limited, Village 9, Floor 26 Salesforce Tower, 110 Bishopsgate, London, EC2N 4AY, United Kingdom)  (  https://www.salesforce.com/content/dam/web/en_us/www/documents/legal/misc/Salesforce-Processor-BCR.pdf )
· Fair Computer Systems, Ostendstr. 132, 90482 Nürnberg, Germany
· IBM GBS France, 17 Avenue de l'Europe, 92275 Bois-Colombes, France
· MRM Worldwide (UK) Ltd, 3 Grosvenor Gardens, London SW1W 0BD
Your name, contact details and vehicle details
Warranty, roadside assistance and aftersales services
Warranty, aftersales and roadside assistance service providers who support Vauxhall in administering the warranty, who provide any extended warranty or roadside assistance or aftersales services to you.
Your name, contact details and vehicle details
Provision of finance in support of your purchase
Vauxhall Finance, Heol-Y-Gamlas, Parc Nantgarw, Treforest, Cardiff, CF15 7QU
Your name, contact details and vehicle details
Provision of insurance
• Europa Insurance, Europa House, Midland Way, Thornbury, Bristol, BS35 2JX
Your name, contact details and vehicle details
Providing your lease plans
• Free2move Lease, a trading division of Peugeot Motor Company Plc of Pinley House, 2 Sunbeam Way, Coventry, CV3 1ND
B. Where necessary in our legitimate interests or those of a third party
The information we share
Why we share it
Who we share it with
Your name and contact details*, product and service specifications*
Market research and consumer surveys to receive feedback related to Vauxhall products and services (e.g. customer satisfaction surveys) and so that we can contact you in these circumstances
Opel Automobile Gmbh and PSA Automobiles SA, 2-10 Boulevard de l’Europe, 78 300 Poissy, France
The above listed recipients disclose your personal information to the respective engaged processors to support the administration of the named purposes
Your name and contact details
(Name*, Phone no.*)
Fulfilment tracking, to monitor our service levels and the service levels of our retailers
TrackBack, 10ACT Limited, 8 Waldegrave Road, Teddington, Middlesex TW11 8HT, United Kingdom
C. Where necessary to comply with a legal obligation that we are subject to
The information we share
Why we share it
Who we share it with
Your identification, contact details and vehicle details
Vehicle registration; Change of ownership notification
The Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency
Keeping your information up to date
To keep your information up to date and deliver the best service to you we will compare details we hold with information held by the Royal Mail National Change of Address register, the DVLA and other national screening services such as deceased registers and Telephone and Mailing Preference Services. Any updated information will be combined with other information we hold to give us the most up to date view of your details and requirements.
3. Interaction with social networks
3.1 Customer care and assistance via Social Media
You may contact us also via our Social Media Channels. E.g., if you send us a message or post something on our Social Media Channels, we may use the information in your message or post to follow-up with you on the issue you contacted us about. We will contact you using the same  Social Media Channel that you used to contact us In order to give you the assistance you requested, we may ask you to provide via direct or private message further information such as details on the issue, name, email, VIN, phone, location (town/county) and/or make, model and year of your vehicle. The information you provide will not be used for direct marketing; market research for service and product improvement in a form that would identify you.
Please note that you should not include any sensitive data (such as information on racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical convictions, or health) in your post or message. Be aware that if you post something on a public Social Media Channel, anyone might be able to read it.
3.2 Links to social networks / social media plug-ins
Our website includes links to social networks.
In order to protect your personal information while visiting our website we do not use social plugins. Instead, HTML-links are embedded onto the website, enabling easy sharing onto social media platforms. Embedding the link prevents a direct connection with various social media network servers when opening a page from our website. When clicking on one of the buttons, a browser window opens and directs the user to the respective service provider website on which (after having logged in) for example; the “Like” or “Share” button can be used.
For more information on the purpose and scope of data processing and further use of your personal information by the provider and their websites as well as your rights and possible settings to protect your privacy, please refer to the data protection information of the relevant service provider.
Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/policy.php
Twitter: https://twitter.com/privacy
Instagram: https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388
You Tube: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-GB
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy
4. If you choose to receive marketing from Vauxhall
By consenting to marketing you agree that your personal details and the information you provide as part of any request, will be processed by Vauxhall Motors Limited ('Vauxhall') as data controller, to provide personalised marketing and for market research purposes.
Your information will be processed and shared for the purposes listed below and with the following recipients:
The information we use
Why we use it
Who we share it with
First name, surname and contact information such as email address, phone number and postal address and any other related information provided by you.
Information about your vehicle including vehicle identification number (VIN), registration number, diagnostic trouble codes, and associated data, e.g. vehicle control unit event data and service history and event prediction detail.
To advise you of our products, services and offers that we think may be of interest to you and to remind you about important events relevant to your vehicle e.g. service reminders.
To get your opinion of Vauxhall products and services : for example we will send satisfaction surveys.
To tailor advertising : We share certain information with advertising and ad placement partners to serve Vauxhall offers which we feel are most relevant to you on your web journeys and social media interactions.
PSA Automobiles SA (Groupe PSA), 2-10 Boulevard de l’Europe 78300 Poissy, France and to the respective engaged processors.
Vauxhall Motors Limited will also share your information with other third parties who provide IT, website hosting and data maintenance services. Such third parties include FCS Fair Computer Services GmbH, Ostendstraße 132, 90482 Nuernberg, Germany and MRM Worldwide (UK) Ltd, 3 Grosvenor Gardens, London SW1W 0BD.
Keeping your information up to date
To keep your information up to date and deliver the best service to you we will share your details with the Royal Mail National Change of Address register, the DVLA and other national screening services such as deceased registers and Telephone and Mailing Preference Services.Your personal information will be stored for the above-mentioned purposes for three years after the last contact with Vauxhall.
We will only contact you for direct marketing purposes where you have given us your consent to do so in accordance with Art. 6 (1) (a) General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)).
IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO STOP RECEIVING MARKETING FROM VAUXHALL
You can withdraw your consent at any time by unsubscribing from any email, emailing privacyrights-vauxhall@mpsa.com, or by writing to us at Privacy Rights, Vauxhall Motors Limited, MP UK1-101-135, Luton Road, Chalton, Luton, LU4 9TT. You should be aware however that withdrawal of consent does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal and that, as Vauxhall Retailers are independent legal entities, you will need to contact them separately to manage the marketing preferences they hold for you.
5. Vauxhall Retailers
When you buy or lease a Vauxhall vehicle or product from a Vauxhall Retailer, the Retailer will share your information with Vauxhall. Please be aware that each Retailer operates as a separate legal entity and you should read the Retailer’s privacy statement to ensure that you understand their privacy practices and procedures. Additionally, because the Vauxhall Retailer often is the first contact with you, the Retailer can answer any questions you may have about their privacy practices.
While Vauxhall encourages its Retailers to ensure full compliance with all applicable privacy legislation and has provided information to our Retailers relating to privacy obligations, Vauxhall is not responsible for Retailers’ compliance with applicable law. When completing a purchase or lease agreement or signing a service repair order with the Vauxhall Retailer, you should be provided with information describing the their privacy practices and related policies that explain that certain personal information that you provide to the Retailer may be shared with Vauxhall or others in accordance with this privacy  policy.
6. Your Rights
As data subject, data protection laws give you a number of rights in relation to your personal information. You have the right to access your personal information, to have your personal information corrected or erased (right to be forgotten). You have the right to restrict the processing of your personal information, to have it transferred to a third party in a commonly structured format. You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information. If you object to your personal information being processed for marketing purposes we will comply with that request. Where you object to other processing, we will consider your request carefully. We do not want to handle your personal information for purposes you do not want us to however, you should be aware that the above-mentioned rights are not absolute and in some circumstances may not apply.
If you want to exercise any of your above-mentioned rights please contact us at by email at privacyrights-vauxhall@mpsa.com or in writing to Privacy Rights, Vauxhall Motors Limited, MP UK1-101-135, Luton Road, Chalton, Luton, Bedfordshire, LU4 9TT .
You can update your personal information at any time by contacting us as above. We will also take steps to update your personal information (e.g. update your address), if we become aware that it has changed.
You also have the  right to lodge a complaintwith the supervisory authority. To do this, you can contact The Information Commissioner’s Office through their website at www.ico.org.uk, by phone on 03031231113 or in writing to Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, SK9 5AF.
7. Changes to the Privacy Policy
All future changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this website. You should therefore periodically review these for changes to our Privacy Policy.
8. Contacting us
You can contact us at any time if you have queries regarding this privacy policy on dataprotectionuk@mpsa.com.
Contact details of the Data Protection Officer:
The Data Protection Officer, Vauxhall Motors Limited, MP UK1-101-135, Luton Road, Chalton, Luton, Bedfordshire, LU4 9TT or by email to dataprotectionuk@mpsa.com.
Version: April 2020
See our Legal Notice for the full company details.
